icseguess.com 2011-05-30

# icse India, icse Board Guess Questions Papers & Results, icse Tutors, Books, Schools India, Indian Educational

Privacy Policy

ICseguess.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices. For additional information about icseguess.com, please review our Terms of Service.   
icseguess.com does not sell or rent your personal identification to third parties. icseguess.com does provide your personal identification to selected, affiliated companies to allow them to perform services for members on our behalf.

Personal Messaging

It is the policy of icseguess.com to send our members only the types of pm they elect to receive in addition to icseguess.com customary business communications (address confirmation, renewal notifications, new product offerings, etc.) Further, it is our policy to remove members from any icseguess.com mailing list to which they have subscribed upon request (members will continue to receive customary business communications from icseguess.com). At any time, members can update their email preferences list via the "My Page" button. In addition, every subscribed email communication from icseguess.com will contain clear and obvious instructions for how the member can remove himself or herself from that mailing list.

Membership Registration

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor your experience at icseguess.com, showing content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. We do this in two ways. First, we analyze member’s information in aggregate - that is, we collect information about thousands of site visits and analyze it as a whole. This kind of study involves looking for trends among many visitors to icseguess.com, rather than analyzing information about any individual member. Examples include researching which parts of the site are accessed most frequently, or determining which products are most attractive to our users. Second, we may use information gathered during your visit to help customize our communications with you.   
icseguess.com may periodically conduct individual voluntary member surveys. We encourage our members to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer, and how we provide them to you. The responses we collect in online surveys are anonymous. In the end, we hope to tailor our communications with you to fit your needs - so that you receive more of what you want from us and less of what you don't want.

Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use our Web site. We use cookies to improve the member experience, like allowing the member to login without typing the registered email address or registration number and password. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major Web sites.

IP Address

Like most Internet sites, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. This information is distributed to current and potential advertisers, but only in aggregate form. It does not contain information that identifies individual members.

Advertising and Third Party Links

Some icseguess.com advertisers and affiliate partners may request information directly from users, or link to sites that do so. icseguess.com has no control over its advertisers' privacy policies, and encourages users to review such policies prior to submitting any personal information to them.  
icseguess.com contains non-advertising links to a variety of third party sites to enhance the member experience. icseguess.com has no control of either the content or privacy policies of such sites, nor should such links be considered an endorsement of these sites except where otherwise noted.

Updates to our information practices

From time to time, we make changes to our information practices or alter the functionality of our Web site. We always update this statement accordingly, so we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on privacy practices at icseguess.com.

Abuse of Terms of Service

We may provide your personal information to the police or other investigating agencies to assist them in the investigation of any suspected violations of law. We also have the right to share your name and contact information with our attorneys in the event of serious violations of conduct.

**Privacy policy FAQ’s**

  1. What information does icseguess.com track 
  2. How does icseguess.com use the information it collects / tracks.
  3. With whom does icseguess.com share the information it collects/tracks. 
  4. What about links to other sites? 
  5. Use of cookies on the site. 
  6. This sites policy on correcting, updating or removing personal information. 
  7. Changes in our privacy policy. 
  8. Security of your personal information. 
  9. Personal mail Choice/Opt-out policy 
  10. Methods of contacting the site.   
Please contact www.icseguess.com with questions regarding this statement. If the website has not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed.

1\. About icseguess.com and the Information We Collect 

icseguess.com which provide facility to students for online syllabus, guess papers, sample papers and guess model. It also provides the facility to student for sending personal mails to tutors. icseguess.com is the complete platform for the icse students, teachers & other directly & indirectly linked with icse. It helps to locate tutors all over India, your school friends, book sellers, educators and strengthens this bond by offering an easy means to keep in touch with each other through, personal messaging (PM), Photo gallery(coming soon), Friend lists etc

Information Collected/Tracked by icseguess.com

icseguess.com gathers two types of information:

     1.information users submit to us and  
     2\. information not directly submitted by users

Information submitted to icseguess.com

There are two types of user-submitted information we collect: Public and Private. We define Public information as personal information that may be displayed on the site, such as gender, age and height, but cannot be linked to a particular user. Private information is defined as any information that allows others to contact a user other than through icseguess.com or allows the collection of information about the user other than what is displayed on the site.

Public: To accomplish our goal of bringing friends and compatible people together, we must gather personal information, which may or may not include: customer-specified icseguess.com username, gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, religion, income range, occupation, preference/lifestyle information and general geographic location. Much of this information is optional, and meant to be seen by members and visitors to the site but cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.

Surveys & Contests: From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, and age).

icseguess.com Affiliate Partners: The Affiliate Partner program is a vehicle for other friends & relationship-based sites to link to icseguess.com. No personal member information is exchanged with the Affiliate Partner. It simply establishes a business relationship with the partner. Affiliate Partners may not view or access private information on icseguess.com subscribers.

Information not Directly Submitted by Users to icseguess.com   
Aggregate: This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site and is used for general management of the site.

**1\. How does icseguess.com share Information Obtained?**

Information users submit to icseguess.com

Surveys & Contests: Contact and other information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information collected will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

icseguess.com’s Affiliate Partners: Information submitted by the Affiliate Partner is used for establishing and maintaining a business relationship. No personal or business information is shared outside the relationship between icseguess.com and the Affiliate Partner. Affiliate Partners may not view or access private information on icseguess.com subscribers.

Information that users do not submit to us

Aggregate: We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general administration of our website.

**2\. Links with other sites**

This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that icseguess.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**3\. Information on Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on icseguess.com site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects a cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas on our site. We occasionally use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site or for advertising tracking purposes. In addition, cookies may be used on our site to allow enhanced capabilities such as chat. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user!

**4\. Info on Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

icseguess.com gives users several options for modifying or removing their information from our database please visit the My Page or contact us.

**5\. Changes in icseguess.com Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner, and we will then use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**6\. What about Email Choice/Opt-out?**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email or by logging-in and changing their email options in the My Page section of the site.

**7\. How to contact icseguess.com?**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
